[{"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int x=1;\n    float y = 1.0;\n    if(x == y)\n    {\n        printf(\"Polo\\n\");\n    }\n    if( 1 == 1.0)\n    {\n        printf(\"Golf\\n\");\n    }\n\n    if( 1.0 == 1.0f )\n    {\n         printf(\"Boxing\\n\");\n    }\n    return 0;\n}", "option1": "A) No Output", "option2": "B) Boxing", "option3": "C) Golf\nBoxing", "option4": "D) Polo\nGolf\nBoxing", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9;\n    if(a=8)\n    {\n        printf(\"Kangaroo\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"Eggs\\n\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) No output", "option2": "B) Eggs", "option3": "C) Kangaroo\nEggs", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9;\n    if(a==5);\n    {\n        printf(\"Kangaroo\\n\");\n    }\n    printf(\"Eggs\\n\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Eggs", "option2": "B) Kangaroo\nEggs", "option3": "C) No output", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9;\n    if(a==9);\n    {\n        printf(\"Ostrich\\n\");\n    }\n    elseif(a==8)\n    {\n        printf(\"Eggs\\n\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"White\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) White", "option2": "B) Ostrich\nWhite", "option3": "C) No Ouput", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9;\n    if(a==9)\n    {\n        printf(\"Ostrich\\n\");\n    }\n    else;\n    {\n        printf(\"Eggs\\n\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"White\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) White", "option2": "B) Ostrich\nWhite", "option3": "C) Ostrich\nEggs\nWhite", "option4": "D) Compiler Error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9, b=5, c=8;\n    a=b=c=10;\n    if(a==9)\n    {\n        printf(\"Ostrich\\n\");\n    }\n    else\n    {\n        printf(\"Eggs\\n\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"White\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Ostrich\nEggs\nWhite", "option2": "B) Ostrich\nWhite", "option3": "C) Eggs\nWhite", "option4": "D) Compiler error as you can not assign to more than two variables at once.", "ans": "C"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9, b=5, c=8;\n\n    if(!(a==9))\n    {\n        printf(\"Bear\\n\");\n    }\n    else\n    {\n        printf(\"Elephant\\n\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"Fox\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Bear\nFox", "option2": "B) Elephant\nFox", "option3": "C) Fox", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the Priority of C Logical Operators.? NOT (!), AND (&&) and OR (||)", "option1": "A) NOT (!) > AND (&&)\u00a0 > OR (||)", "option2": "B) NOT (!) > AND (&&)\u00a0= OR (||)", "option3": "C) AND (&&) >\u00a0OR (||) > NOT (!)", "option4": "D) AND (&&) =\u00a0OR (||) > NOT (!)", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9, b;\n    \n    b = (a==9) ? (printf(\"CAT\\n\");printf(\"DOG\\n\")) : (printf(\"FOX\"));\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) CAT\nDOG", "option2": "B) FOX", "option3": "C) CAT\nDOG\nFOX", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9, b=6;\n    if(a==9 && b==6)\n    {\n        printf(\"Hockey\");\n    }\n    else\n    {\n        printf(\"Cricket\");\n    }\n    \n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Cricket\nFootball", "option2": "B) Hockey\nFootball", "option3": "C) Football", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=9, b=6;\n    if(a!=9 || b==6)\n    {\n        printf(\"Hockey\\n\");\n    }\n    else\n    {\n        printf(\"Cricket\\n\");\n    }\n    \n    printf(\"Football\");\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Cricket\nFootball", "option2": "B) Hockey\nFootball", "option3": "C) Football", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " Choose a correct C Operator Priority.?\nItems in one group ( ) has same priority.", "option1": "A) ( ! ) <\u00a0(*, /, %) <\u00a0(+, -) <\u00a0( <, <=, >, >=) <\u00a0(==, !=) <\u00a0(&&) <\u00a0(||) <\u00a0(=)", "option2": "B) (( ! ) ,\u00a0(*, /, %) ,\u00a0(+, -)) <\u00a0( <, <=, >, >=) <\u00a0(==, !=) <\u00a0(&&) <\u00a0(||) <\u00a0(=)", "option3": "C) ( ! ) > (*, /, %) > (+, -) > ( <, <=, >, >=) > (==, !=) > (&&) > (||) > (=)", "option4": "D) (( ! ) ,\u00a0(*, /, %) ,\u00a0(+, -)) >\u00a0( <, <=, >, >=) >\u00a0(==, !=) >\u00a0(&&) >\u00a0(||) >\u00a0(=)", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=5, b=8;\n    \n    if( a==5 && (b=9) )\n    {\n        printf(\"Gorilla Glass=\");\n    }\n    printf(\"%d %d\", a, b);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 5 8", "option2": "B) 5 9", "option3": "C) Gorilla Glass=5 8", "option4": "D) Gorilla Glass=5 9", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=5, b=8;\n    \n    if( a==5 || (b=9) )\n    {\n        printf(\"Gorilla Glass=\");\n    }\n    printf(\"%d %d\", a, b);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 5 8", "option2": "B) 5 9", "option3": "C) Gorilla Glass=5 8", "option4": "D) Gorilla Glass=5 9", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Choose a correct C Statement.", "option1": "A) Nesting of ? : operator is possible.", "option2": "B) int main()\n{\n    int a=5, b=8;\n    \n    if( a>=5 || (b=9) )\n    {\n        printf(\"Gorilla Glass\");\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n//OUTPUT: Gorilla Glass\n", "option3": "C) int main()\n{\n    int a=5, b=8;\n    \n    if( a >= 5 && b <= 9 )\n    {\n        printf(\"Gorilla Glass\");\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n//OUTPUT: Gorilla Glass\n", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}]
